<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>Digital Inovator - Innovation for Your Business</title>
	<be>Be Inovator</be>
	<menu>
		<services>Services</services>
		<portfolio>Portfolio</portfolio>
		<about>About</about>
		<hireme>Hire me</hireme>
		<contact>Contact</contact>
		<idiom>idiom</idiom>
	</menu>

	<buttons>
		<vitae>download resume(Pt)</vitae>
		<portfolio>See portfolio</portfolio>
		<about>About</about>
		<hireme>Hire me</hireme>
		<send>Send</send>
	</buttons>

	<idiom>
		<pt>Portuguese</pt>
		<en>English</en>
		<es>Spanish</es>
	</idiom>

	<pages>
		<services>
			<title>SERVICES</title>
			<description>Services I can offer.</description>
			<types>
				<web>
					<title>Web</title>
					<description>Sites, Hot Sites, Web Systems, E-commerce, Social Networks, SEO (Search Engine Optmization).</description>
				</web>
				<image>
					<title>Image and Video Editing</title>
					<description>Treatment, corrections, special effects, vignettes, intros, makingoffs.</description>
				</image>
				<photo>
					<title>Photography</title>
					<description>Creative Photo Essays, Product photography, Business photography.</description>
				</photo>

			</types>
		</services>
		<portfolio>
			<title>PORTFOLIO</title>
			<description>Some of my works.</description>
		</portfolio>

		<about>
			<title>ABOUT</title>
			<description>"Everyone in this country should learn to program".</description>
			<content><![CDATA[
				<p class="text-muted"><img class="img-circle img-responsive" src="img/about/_MG_5549.jpg" alt="" width="200" style="float: left; margin-right: 10px"> Hello, how is it going? My name is Wesin Alves, I have a degree in Computer Engineering from the Federal University of Pará (2007) and a Master's degree in Electrical Engineering from the Federal University of Pará (2011). I am currently a student of the PhD course of the Graduate Program in Electrical Engineering - Federal University of Pará. I have experience in the area of Software Development for Web and Computational Intelligence, working mainly in the following topics: Machine Learning, Data Mining, Artificial Neural Networks, Atypical Detection, Reinforcement Learning, PHP, Java, PostgreSql, Mysql and UML.</p>

                    <p class="text-muted">I have a fairly solid background in the area of computing covering several areas, but the focus of my activities over the years has been web development. I have been a developer in several state government agencies where I have always worked in this area. I have a dream of helping people connect through a digital initiative because I believe that the connected world is a better world.</p>

                    <p class="text-muted">I agree with one of the phrases that Steve Jobs, one of the great digital innovators of the world, said: "Everyone in this country should learn how to program".</p>
				]]></content>
		</about>

		<hireme>
			<title>HIRE ME</title>
			<description>Everyone needs to connect to the internet.</description>
			<content><![CDATA[
				<p class="text-muted"><img class="img-circle img-responsive" src="img/about/3.jpg" alt="" style="float: left; margin-right: 10px"> You can hire me to create your brand, website, system, visual identity, image editing, video creation, vignettes, intros, promotions, photo essays, product and business photography.</p>
                    <p class="text-muted">I am available for remote jobs in freelance or home-office projects. I am also available for travel.</p> 
                    <p class="text-muted">In freelance projects, I work such with a fixed amount per hour that per project. Feel free to contact me and ask questions about the process we use to develop our work or talk about an employment opportunity.</p> 
				]]></content>
		</hireme>

		<contact>
			<title>CONTACT</title>			
			<description><![CDATA[Fill in the fields and click submit. Whatsapp: (+55 91) 98197-1595.]]></description>
			<fields>
				<name>Name *</name>
				<email>Email *</email>
				<phone>Phone *</phone>
				<message>Tell me about your project, including some timeline and technological expectations *</message>
				<budget>What is your project budget?</budget>
			</fields>
		</contact>
	</pages>
	<currency>US$ </currency>
	<terms>
		Terms
	</terms>
	<privacy>
		Privacy policy
	</privacy>

	<phrases>
		<phrase id='1'>
			<content>Most good programmers do not program for money or for applause, they do it because it's fun to program</content>
			<author>Linus Torvalds</author>
		</phrase>
		<phrase id='2'>
			<content>Your idea will not matter if you can not convince someone.</content>
			<author>Inovador Digital</author>
		</phrase>

		<phrase id='3'>
			<content>Never stop at the first step. Otherwise, you'll never get to the top.</content>
			<author>Inovador Digital</author>
		</phrase>
	</phrases>

</text>